<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="about">
        Spendid is an expense tracking application that allows users to create records of the transactions that they have made,
        and store them in virtual wallets, to allow for ease of tracking of their expenses.
    </string>
    <string name="developers">
        If you enjoy using Spendid, consider following us, the developers, on social media.
    </string>
    <string name="api_diclaimer">
        Spendid uses a currency exchange rate API created by Fawaz Ahmed, and is NOT affiliated, endorsed or supported by Fawaz Ahmed.
    </string>
    <string name="icon_credits">
        FreePik. (nd). Australia Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010

        FreePik. (nd). Brazil Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010

        FreePik. (nd). Canada Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010

        FreePik. (nd). Chile Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010

        FreePik. (nd). China Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010

        FreePik. (nd). Colombia Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010
        FreePik. (nd). Czech Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010
        FreePik. (nd). Denmark Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010
        FreePik. (nd). European Union Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010
        FreePik. (nd). Hong Kong Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010
        FreePik. (nd). Hungary Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010
        FreePik. (nd). India Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010
        FreePik. (nd). Indonesia Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010
        FreePik. (nd). Israel Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010
        FreePik. (nd). Japan Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010
        FreePik. (nd). Malaysia Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010
        FreePik. (nd). Mexico Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010
        FreePik. (nd). New Zealand Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010
        FreePik. (nd). Norway Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010
        FreePik. (nd). Philippines Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010
        FreePik. (nd). Poland Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010
        FreePik. (nd). Romania Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010
        FreePik. (nd). Russia Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010
        FreePik. (nd). Saudi Arabia Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010
        FreePik. (nd). Singapore Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010
        FreePik. (nd). South Africa Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010
        FreePik. (nd). South Korea Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010
        FreePik. (nd). Sweden Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010
        FreePik. (nd). Switzerland Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010
        FreePik. (nd). Taiwan Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010
        FreePik. (nd). Thailand Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010
        FreePik. (nd). Turkey Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010
        FreePik. (nd). United Arab Emirates Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010
        FreePik. (nd). United Kingdom Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010
        FreePik. (nd). United States Flag. Retrieved from http://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/call-center-worker-with-headset_46010

        Country flags by Freepik, from www.flaticon.coms
    </string>
</resources>